<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Talkback Tutorial</string>
    <string name="lesson1_title">Lesson 1</string>
    <string name="lesson1_subtitle">Single Motion Gestures</string>
    <string name="lesson2_title">Lesson 2</string>
    <string name="lesson2_subtitle">Multi-Finger Gestures</string>
    <string name="lesson3_title">Lesson 3</string>
    <string name="lesson3_subtitle">Dual Motion Gestures</string>
    <string name="lesson4_title">Lesson 4</string>
    <string name="lesson4_subtitle">Typing</string>
    <string name="lessons">Lessons</string>
    <string name="adjust_reading_controls_part1_intro">This module covers how to adjust TalkBack\'s reading controls, which lets us make TalkBack read and navigate in different ways. When you change modes, TalkBack will speak the mode you switched to.</string>
    <string name="adjust_reading_controls_part1_prompt">To change your mode, swipe up and down in one motion. Try to go through all of the options before moving on.</string>
    <string name="adjust_reading_controls_part1_backwards_prompt">You can go backwards through the list. Swipe down then up in one motion to go through the list in the opposite direction.</string>
    <string name="adjust_reading_controls_part1_multi_finger">Modes can also be switched by swiping with three fingers horizontally either to the left or to the right. Try going through the list with three finger swipes in both directions before moving on.</string>
    <string name="adjust_reading_controls_part1_finished_text">That\'s all there is to changing modes. The rest of this lesson covers how to use these modes. Activate the button below to finish this module.</string>
    <string name="finish_module_button">Finish module</string>
    <string name="jump_controls_intro_initial_text">The \"Controls\" reading mode allows jumping between buttons, sliders, switches, and other interactive things.</string>
    <string name="jump_controls_intro_first_prompt">Switch to the Controls reading mode and swipe down to jump to the next button.</string>
    <string name="wrong_action_message">You performed the wrong action. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="pushback_text">This element will push you back</string>
    <string name="adjust_reading_controls_part1_justification">There are reading and navigation modes. Reading modes help you read in a granular way, such as by words, paragraphs, or characters. Navigation modes help you move around more efficiently, such as by jumping from button to button.</string>
    <string name="finish_module">Finish Module</string>
    <string name="jump_text_paragraph_can">Can you can a canned can into an un-canned can like a canner can can a canned can into an un-canned can?</string>
    <string name="jump_text_paragraph_seashells">She sells seashells on the seashore. The shells she sells are seashells, I’m sure. And if she sells seashells on the seashore, Then I’m sure she sells seashore shells.</string>
    <string name="jump_text_paragraph_piper">Peter Piper picked a peck of pickled peppers; A peck of pickled peppers Peter Piper picked; If Peter Piper picked a peck of pickled peppers, Where’s the peck of pickled peppers Peter Piper picked</string>
    <string name="jump_navigation_easy_first_element">There\'s another %s below. Jump to it.</string>
    <string name="jump_navigation_easy_last_element">This is the last %s. Activate it to continue.</string>
    <string name="jump_navigation_easy_last_element_active">To continue, swipe up to the previous %s</string>
    <string name="jump_navigation_easy_first_element_active">That\'s the basics of jumping between %s. Activate to %s.</string>
    <string name="jump_headers_entity">header</string>
    <string name="jump_headers_entity_plural">headers</string>
    <string name="jump_controls_entity">control</string>
    <string name="jump_controls_entity_plural">controls</string>
    <string name="jump_links_entity">link</string>
    <string name="jump_links_entity_plural">links</string>
    <string name="final_button_mid_module_prompt">continue</string>
    <string name="final_button_end_module_prompt">finish module</string>
    <string name="jump_headers_intro_1">The \"Headers\" reading mode allows you to jump between headers, such those found before blocks of text or groups of form fields.</string>
    <string name="jump_links_intro_1">The \"Links\" navigation mode lets you jump between clickable links on a page, such as a URL.</string>
    <string name="jump_text_request_paragraph_mode">We will now learn to use each reading modes. As you have learned previously, please switch to the reading mode that says \"Paragraph\"</string>
    <string name="jump_text_paragraphs_intro">You will now learn to transition between paragraphs. A single swipe up or down will transition between different paragraphs that are on the screen. Please try it until you reach a button that says finish lesson, then double tap to finish the lesson. For your information, this will be a very long practice text so it would be easier to complete it using the Paragraph reading mode. However, you can still try out different reading modes such as Characters, Words and lines reading modes.</string>
    <string name="jump_text_paragraphs_conclusion">You have completed the lesson. To summarise, in this lesson you have learnt to use the Paragraph reading mode to navigate through the page. In the future, you can utilise these different reading modes such as Headers, Controls, Links and more, to navigate through your phone. Sending you back to the Lesson modules.</string>
</resources>