<resources>

    <!-- General !-->
    <string name="intent_key">C57D2EB9-C8D0-4315-916D-C05159E8EE23</string>
    <string name="app_name">Talkback Tutorial</string>
    <string name="lessons">Lessons</string>
    <string name="nl">\n</string>
    <string name="underscore">_</string>
    <string name="lesson_space">"Lesson "</string>
    <string name="finish_lesson">Finish Lesson</string>
    <string name="finish_lesson_button">FinishLesson</string>
    <string name="continue_jump_text">Continue module</string>
    <string name="finish_module_button">Finish module</string>
    <string name="finish">Finish</string>
    <string name="row">Row</string>
    <string name="column1">Column1</string>
    <string name="column2">Column2</string>
    <string name="column3">Column3</string>
    <string name="a">a</string>
    <string name="hello">hello</string>
    <string name="repeat_instructions">repeat instructions</string>
    <string name="continue_str">Continue</string>
    <string name="continue_button">Continue</string>
    <string name="input">Input</string>
    <string name="android">android</string>
    <string name="forward_slash">/</string>
    <string name="menu_item">Menu Item</string>
    <string name="android_resource">android.resource://</string>
    <string name="empty_string">" "</string>
    <string name="back_button">Back</string>
    <string name="lesson_page_back_button">Go back to the main menu</string>

    <!-- Lessons !-->
    <string name="lesson1_title">Getting Started</string>
    <string name="lesson2_title">Basic Menu Navigation</string>
    <string name="lesson2_desc">This lesson covers the basics of Android navigation using Talkback</string>
    <string name="lesson3_title">Controlling Reading</string>
    <string name="lesson3_desc">This lesson covers how to change the reading settings of Talkback</string>
    <string name="lesson4_title">Interacting with Media</string>
    <string name="lesson4_desc">This lesson covers the gestures and action needed to interact with media using Talkback</string>
    <string name="lesson5_title">Advanced Menu Navigation</string>
    <string name="lesson5_desc">This lesson covers how to navigate more complex Android menus using Talkback</string>
    <string name="lesson6_title">Typing Lesson</string>
    <string name="lesson6_desc">These cover the gestures and actions needed to use the virtual keyboard through Talkback</string>
    <string name="lesson7_title">External Apps</string>
    <string name="lesson7_desc">This lesson provides real world experience by having you jump to other applications through Talkback</string>

    <!-- Challenges !-->
    <string name="challenge_outro">You have completed the challenge. Sending you back to the main menu.</string>

    <!-- Lesson 2 Challenge !-->
    <string name="aud">AUD</string>
    <string name="inspect_toy">inspectToy</string>
    <string name="tennis_ball">Tennis Ball</string>
    <string name="tennis_racquet">Tennis Racquet</string>
    <string name="lesson2_challenge_intro">Welcome to Lesson 2\'s challenge. In challenges, you\'ll be presented with practical scenarios to demonstrate your newly learnt skills. In this challenge, you\'ll be presented with a store and must add the tennis ball and the tennis racquet to your watchlist to complete the challenge. The tennis ball has a price of $5, and the tennis racquet has a price of $180. You may now start.</string>
    <string name="rating_content_description">Rating: %1$d stars</string>

    <!-- Lesson 3 Challenge !-->
    <string name="lesson3_challenge_intro">Welcome to Lesson 3\'s challenge. In this challenge you will be presented with a page containing baking recipes. Feel free to navigate through the different page elements using the appropriate reading controls. To complete the challenge, navigate to the cookie recipe and check the checkbox for the following ingredient … 1 egg</string>
    <string name="recipe_book_title">Baking Recipes</string>
    <string name="cookie_header">Cookies</string>
    <string name="cookie_img_desc">Picture of a cookie</string>
    <string name="cookie_description">This scrumptious and chewy chocolate-chip cookie recipe is guaranteed to satisfy your sweet tooth!</string>
    <string name="cookie_link"><a href="http://www.google.com">Get cookie recipe</a></string>
    <string name="brownie_header">Brownies</string>
    <string name="brownie_img_desc">Picture of a brownie</string>
    <string name="brownie_description">This gooey brownie recipe is a crowd pleaser and is so quick and easy to make!</string>
    <string name="brownie_link"><a href="http://www.google.com">Get brownie recipe</a></string>
    <string name="ingredients_heading">Ingredients</string>
    <string name="method_heading">Method</string>
    <string name="lesson3_challenge_outro">You have successfully completed Lesson 3\'s challenge. Sending you to the main menu.</string>
    <!-- Cookie Recipe !-->
    <string name="cookie_recipe_title">Cookie Recipe</string>
    <string name="cookie_recipe_ingredient_1">½ cup of white sugar</string>
    <string name="cookie_recipe_ingredient_2">½ cup of brown sugar</string>
    <string name="cookie_recipe_ingredient_3">150 grams of softened butter</string>
    <string name="cookie_recipe_ingredient_4">1 teaspoon of vanilla extract</string>
    <string name="cookie_recipe_ingredient_5">1 and ¾ cups of plain flour</string>
    <string name="cookie_recipe_ingredient_6">1 egg</string>
    <string name="cookie_recipe_ingredient_7">1 cup of chocolate chips</string>
    <string name="cookie_recipe_method_1">Step 1: Preheat oven to 180C or 160C fan–forced. Line 2 baking trays with baking paper. Using an electric mixer or whisking by hand, beat butter and sugars, and 1–2 minutes or until smooth and well combined. Beat in egg and vanilla until combined.</string>
    <string name="cookie_recipe_method_2">Step 2: Stir in flour. Stir in chocolate chips. Roll 2 level tablespoonfuls of mixture into balls and place on prepared trays, 3cm apart. Press down slightly. Decorate with extra chocolate chips.</string>
    <string name="cookie_recipe_method_3">Step 3: Bake for 15–18 minutes or until light golden and cooked. Transfer to a wire rack to cool. Store in an airtight container for up to 1 week.</string>
    <!-- Brownie Recipe !-->
    <string name="brownie_recipe_title">Brownie Recipe</string>
    <string name="brownie_recipe_ingredient_1">125 grams of unsalted butter</string>
    <string name="brownie_recipe_ingredient_2">125 grams of dark baking chocolate</string>
    <string name="brownie_recipe_ingredient_3">3 eggs, lightly whisked</string>
    <string name="brownie_recipe_ingredient_4">1 and ½ cups of white sugar</string>
    <string name="brownie_recipe_ingredient_5">¾ cups of plain flour</string>
    <string name="brownie_recipe_ingredient_6">¼ cup of Dutch cocoa powder</string>
    <string name="brownie_recipe_ingredient_7">1 teaspoon of vanilla extract</string>
    <string name="brownie_recipe_ingredient_8">Pinch of salt</string>
    <string name="brownie_recipe_method_1">Step 1: Preheat oven to 180C or 160C fan forced. Grease a 20cm square cake pan and line with baking paper. </string>
    <string name="brownie_recipe_method_2">Step 2: Place butter and chocolate in a heatproof bowl over a saucepan of simmering water (don\'t let the bowl touch the water). Stir with a metal spoon until melted. Remove from heat. Quickly stir in egg, sugar, flour, cocoa powder, vanilla and salt until just combined. Pour into prepared pan.</string>
    <string name="brownie_recipe_method_3">Step 3: Bake for 30 minutes or until a skewer inserted in the centre comes out with moist crumbs clinging. Set aside to cool completely.</string>


    <!-- Lesson 4 Challenge !-->
    <string name="lesson4_challenge_intro">In this challenge, you\'ll be presented an article with an embedded video already playing. To complete the challenge, pause the video, and return its slider to the beginning of the video, then replay it. You may now start.</string>

    <!-- Lesson 5 Challenge !-->
    <string name="lesson5_challenge_intro">Welcome to Lesson 5\'s challenge. In this challenge, you\'ll perform a sequence of tasks.</string>
    <string name="lesson5_challenge_fragment1_intro">First, go to the home screen and back to this app to receive your next task.</string>
    <string name="lesson5_challenge_fragment2_intro">Welcome back. Now a new message will be sent from Billy, open the notification to hear your next task.</string>
    <string name="lesson5_challenge_notification_title">Billy\'s message</string>
    <string name="lesson5_challenge_outro">Hello, It\'s Billy. Complete this challenge by interacting with this message in the notification panel.</string>
    <string name="lesson5_challenge_part2_backstack">lesson5ChallengePart2</string>
    <string name="lesson5_challenge_part2_notification_name">Talkback tutorial</string>
    <string name="lesson5_challenge_part2_notification_desc">Notification description</string>
    <string name="lesson5_challenge_complete">You\'ve completed Lesson 5\'s challenge, and have been sent to the main menu.</string>

    <!-- Lesson 6 Challenge !-->
    <string name="lesson6_challenge_intro">Welcome to Lesson 6\'s challenge. In this challenge, you\'ll be asked to send a message to your friend, Bob, in a chat room. Now let\'s get started</string>
    <string name="lesson6_challenge_fragment1_intro">To finish this challenge send a message to Bob and include his name.</string>
    <string name="lesson6_challenge_text_message">bob</string>

    <!-- Lesson 1 !-->
    <string name="lesson1_part1_intro">Welcome. In your first lesson, you will learn to move forwards and backwards between menu items, as well as interact with them. Double tap to continue.</string>
    <string name="lesson1_part2_backstack">lesson1part2</string>
    <string name="lesson1_part3_backstack">lesson1part3</string>
    <string name="lesson1_part2_intro">To start, you will learn to navigate back and forth between elements on the screen. To go to the next element, swipe right. To go to the previous element, swipe left. Elements will always speak a description of themselves. When you are ready to move on, double tap. You may now begin.</string>
    <string name="lesson1_menu_item_prompt">You have interacted with a menu item. Find the button, then double tap to finish the lesson.</string>
    <string name="lesson1_lesson_complete">You have completed the lesson. Sending you to the main menu.</string>
    <string name="lesson1_part3_intro">You will now learn to interact with elements on the screen. To interact with an element, double tap when you have selected it. For this activity, explore the elements on the screen until you reach the button. To activate the button and finish the lesson, double tap.</string>

    <!-- AdjustReadingControls !-->
    <string name="adjust_reading_controls_part1_change_to_manual_mode">For modules in this lesson, you\'ll need to use horizontal swipes to navigate yourself through the module content.</string>
    <string name="adjust_reading_controls_part1_intro">This module covers how to adjust TalkBack\'s reading controls, which lets us make TalkBack read and navigate in different ways. When you change modes, TalkBack will speak the mode you have switched to and what you\'re able to do with them.</string>
    <string name="adjust_reading_controls_part1_justification">There are reading and navigation modes. Reading modes help you read in a granular way, such as by words, paragraphs, or characters. Navigation modes help you move around more efficiently, such as by jumping from button to button.</string>
    <string name="adjust_reading_controls_part1_prompt">To change your mode, swipe up and down in one motion. Try to go through all of the options before moving on.</string>
    <string name="adjust_reading_controls_part1_backwards_prompt">You can go backwards through the list. Swipe down then up in one motion to go through the list in the opposite direction.</string>
    <string name="adjust_reading_controls_part1_multi_finger">Modes can also be switched by swiping with three fingers horizontally either to the left or to the right. Try going through the list with three finger swipes in both directions before moving on.</string>
    <string name="adjust_reading_controls_part1_finished_text">That\'s all there is to changing modes. The rest of this lesson covers how to use these modes. Activate the button below to finish this module.</string>

    <!-- Adjust Slider !-->
    <string name="percentage">%</string> <!--not complete!-->
    <string name="adjust_slider_part2_backstack">adjustSliderModulePart2</string>
    <string name="adjust_slider_part1_intro">Welcome. In this module, you will learn how to increase and decrease slider values. A slider is a track that contains values between a minimum and a maximum. Sliders are often used to adjust volume and song times or video times. To start you will try increasing a sliders value. To increase a slider, swipe up. To continue, increase the slider value to 100%</string>
    <string name="adjust_slider_part1_go_to_min">Well done! Now you will try decreasing the sliders value. To decrease a slider, swipe down. To continue set the slider value to 50%</string>
    <string name="adjust_slider_part1_outro">Well done! You now know how to adjust a slider by swiping up or down. You will now be taken to the next part of this lesson</string>
    <string name="adjust_slider_part2_intro">Welcome to the next part of the module. Another way of adjusting sliders is to double tap then drag. To start you will try increasing the sliders value. To increase a slider double tap and hold the slider then drag right. To continue increase the slider value to 100%. Note that you will have to explore by touch to find the slider.</string>
    <string name="adjust_slider_part2_go_to_min">Now you will try decreasing the sliders value. To decrease a slider double tap and hold then drag left. To continue decrease the slider value to 0%.</string>
    <string name="adjust_slider_part2_outro">Well done! now you know how to adjust sliders by dragging. This gesture can be used for any slider, but will be most useful for adjusting video and song times.</string>

    <!-- CalculatorApp !-->
    <string name="tbt">TBT</string>
    <string name="sc">SC</string>
    <string name="action">_ACTION</string>
    <string name="task_finish_calculator">_TASK_FINISH_CALCULATOR</string>
    <string name="calculator_app_pkg">com.simplemobiletools.calculatorapp.debug</string> <!--not complete!-->
    <string name="calculator_app_cls">com.simplemobiletools.calculator.activities.SplashActivity.Orange</string> <!--not complete!-->
    <string name="calculator_app_part1_pkg">com.simplemobiletools.calculator.debug</string>
    <string name="calculator_app_part1_cls">com.simplemobiletools.calculator.activities.SplashActivity.Orange</string>
    <string name="calculator_app_debug">"com.simplemobiletools.calculator.debug"</string>
    <string name="calculator_app_part1_intro">In this module, you will apply what you have learnt from the previous lessons to use the simple calculator app. You will be given a simple calculation task to work on. Unless you complete this task successfully, we will let you retry as many times.</string>
    <string name="calculator_app_part2_intro">Well done! You have successfully completed this module. We have sent you back to the talkback tutorial. You may now move on to the next part.</string>
    <string name="finish_calculator_module">Sending you back to the main module page</string>
    <string name="finish_module">Finish Module</string>
    <string name="equation_calculator_app">In this task, please provide the correct calculation for 9 × 5 to get the result 45. Hint: You may need to explore by touch to find the correct buttons.</string>
    <string name="calculator_not_installed_message">Calculator is not installed. Please install it and reopen this module.</string>
    <string name="calculator_install_intro">In this module, you\'ll be doing a few tasks in a modified version of the Simple Calculator app. You can retrieve this modified app from the link below:</string>
    <string name="calculator_link">"Link to the modified Simple Calculator "</string>
    <string name="calculator_install_prompt">Once you have  installed the app, activate the button below to continue.</string>
    <string name="simple_calculator_link"><a href="https://github.com/TalkbackTutorial/calculator-fork/releases/download/5.10.0-tbfork-2/tbt-simple-calculator-fork.apk">Link to the modified Simple Calculator</a></string>

    <!-- ExploreByTouch !-->
    <string name="explore_menu_by_touch_menu_item_prompt">You have interacted with a menu item. Find the button, then double tap to finish the lesson.</string>
    <string name="explore_menu_by_touch_part1_intro">Welcome! In this module, you will learn how to use explore by touch. You can select different elements by holding your finger on the screen and moving it over another element you\'d like to select. To complete the lesson, use explore by touch to find the Finish Lesson button. Remember to drag your finger in any direction slowly around screen, and make sure your finger is touching the screen at all times. You may now start.</string>
    <string name="explore_menu_by_touch_part1_outro">You have completed the lesson. Sending you to the lesson page.</string>

    <!-- GoBack !-->
    <string name="go_back_part1_intro">Welcome. In this lesson, you will learn how to go back to the previous page. To open the next page, double tap to click the continue button.</string>
    <string name="go_back_part1_outro">You have successfully navigated to the previous page. Lesson complete. Sending you to the main menu.</string>
    <string name="go_back_part2_intro">To navigate back to the previous page, swipe down then left.</string>
    <string name="go_back_part2_backstack">gobackModulePart2</string>

    <!-- GoToHomeScreen !-->
    <string name="stopped_count">stoppedCount</string>
    <string name="go_to_home_screen_intro">Welcome. In this module, you will learn how to return to the home screen from inside an application. To perform do this, perform a swipe up then left gesture. Once complete, open the recents menu by swiping left then up. From the recents menu, return to the tutorial by double tapping the app. You may now start.</string>
    <string name="go_to_home_screen_mid">Good job! This gesture is useful as it allows you to return to the home screen at anytime, no matter where you are. Now do it again, remember: the gesture is swipe up then left. Return to the tutorial through the recents menu just like before. You may now start.</string>
    <string name="go_to_home_screen_outro">Nice work! You have navigated back to the tutorial. You have now learnt how to use the go to home screen gesture. Double tap to return to the lesson page.</string>

    <!-- JumpControls !-->
    <string name="jump_controls_intro_initial_text">The controls reading mode lets you move from one control to the next. Controls can be buttons or switches that you can click, sliders that you can move around, or anything else that you can press or manipulate.</string>
    <string name="jump_controls_entity">control</string>
    <string name="jump_controls_entity_plural">controls</string>

    <!-- JumpHeaders !-->
    <string name="jump_headers_entity">header</string>
    <string name="jump_headers_entity_plural">headers</string>
    <string name="jump_headers_intro_1">The headers reading mode allows you to jump between headers, such as those found before blocks of text or groups of form fields.</string>

    <!-- JumpLinks !-->
    <string name="jump_links_entity">link</string>
    <string name="jump_links_entity_plural">links</string>
    <string name="jump_links_intro_1">The links navigation mode lets you jump between clickable links on a page. Links are short pieces of text that stand in place of an address, such as a URL or website link, that can be activated with a double tap to take you to that address. Not all links can be reached by jumping in this navigation mode, however all of the links in this lesson will work.</string>

    <!-- JumpNavigation !-->
    <string name="jump_navigation_easy_first_element">There\'s another %s below. Jump to it.</string>
    <string name="jump_navigation_easy_last_element">This is the last %s. Activate it to continue.</string>
    <string name="jump_navigation_easy_last_element_active">To continue, swipe up to the previous %s</string>
    <string name="jump_navigation_easy_first_element_active">That\'s the basics of jumping between %s. Activate to %s.</string>
    <string name="jump_navigation_easy_prompt">Switch to the %s reading mode and swipe down to jump to the next %s.</string>
    <string name="jump_navigation_target_link_template"><![CDATA[<a href="http://google.com">%s</a>]]></string>
    <string name="percent_s">%s</string>

    <!-- JumpText !-->
    <string name="jump_text_paragraph_element_1">This is paragraph 1 of 4. When you swipe once up or down in paragraph mode, TalkBack will switch to reading one paragraph at a time, as opposed to reading every paragraph in a block such as the next paragraph. Swipe down until you can reach paragraph 2. If you go too far, you can swipe up to go to the previous paragraph. Please swipe down now.\n\nThis is paragraph 2. If you jump again, you will hear what sounds like a thud and you will not move to the next paragraph. To continue, you will need to swipe down again after that sound.</string>
    <string name="jump_text_paragraph_element_2">This is paragraph 3. What you encountered just now was you reaching another item. Items are what you were navigating earlier using horizontal swipes. When these jumps take you to a new item, you need to swipe again to actually move. Please swipe down to go to the next item.</string>
    <string name="jump_text_paragraph_element_3">This is paragraph 4. Every time you reach a new item, TalkBack will read that particular item from start to end before you continue with vertical swipes. You will also encounter this scenario in the other reading modes that you will learn later. To continue to the next module, please go to the next item and double tap to continue</string>
    <string name="jump_text_paragraph_element_4">Activate this with a double tap to continue.</string>
    <string name="jump_text_request_paragraph_mode">We will now learn to use each text reading mode. As you have learned previously, please switch to the reading mode that says \"Paragraph\"</string>
    <string name="jump_text_paragraphs_intro3"> We will continue to learn to use the word reading mode. As you have familiarized yourself with the reading modes previously, please try this yourself and navigate to the continue word, then double tap to proceed </string>
    <string name="jump_text_paragraphs_intro4"> Finally in this module, use the character reading mode to navigate to the letter "T". When you find it, double tap to finish this module</string>
    <string name="jump_text_paragraphs_conclusion">You have completed this module. To summarise, in this module you have learnt to use all text reading modes to navigate through a page. Sending you back to the Lesson modules.</string>
    <string name="jump_text_continue_fragment_message">We will now learn to use each text reading mode. As you have learned previously, please switch to the reading mode that says Paragraph. If you have changed reading mode to Paragraph mode, Please double tap to continue</string>
    <string name="jump_text_line_intro">Please switch to the lines reading mode and swipe horizontally to go to the next item.</string>
    <string name="jump_text_line_1">Lines mode moves between lines of text, such as this paragraph which wraps into several rows. When you start navigating lines, you\'ll hear only parts of this paragraph at a time. Swipe down now and go through the 5 numbered lines.\nLine 1 of 5. This mode is similar to paragraphs mode.\nLine 2 of 5. The next line is in another item.</string>
    <string name="jump_text_line_2">Line 3 of 5. When first entering an item, all lines may be read.\nLine 4 of 5. If so, you\'ll hear the first line twice.</string>
    <string name="jump_text_line_3">Line 5 of 5. Activate the button below to continue.</string>
    <string name="jump_text_word_intro">The words reading mode lets you jump from word to word. This can be quite slow. Please switch to the words reading mode and go to the next item with a horizontal swipe.</string>
    <string name="jump_text_word_1">Start swiping down.</string>
    <string name="jump_text_word_2">Even when swiping down, you\'ll hear the whole item once.</string>
    <string name="jump_text_word_3">Double tap to continue.</string>
    <string name="jump_text_char_0">C</string>
    <string name="jump_text_char_1">ON</string>
    <string name="jump_text_char_2">T</string>
    <string name="jump_text_char_3">INUE</string>

    <!-- MediaVolumeControl !-->
    <string name="media_volume_control_part1_intro">In this tutorial, you will be learning how to control media volume sliders to adjust volume. To start, find the play button then double tap to play the music.</string>
    <string name="media_volume_control_part1_increase_volume">Great job! Now, go back to the slider and increase the media\'s volume above 75 by swiping up.</string>
    <string name="media_volume_control_part1_play_prompt">The song is not played. Please press the play button to play the music.</string>
    <string name="media_volume_control_part1_talkback_prompt">Talkback is currently not turned on. Please turn Talkback on to continue this lesson</string>
    <string name="media_volume_control_part1_decrease_volume">Current volume is set above 75. Now that you\'ve learned how to increase the volume, we will try decreasing the volume below 25. To decrease the volume, swipe down.</string>
    <string name="media_volume_control_part1_outro">Current volume is set below 25. Congratulations on completing this lesson. Sending you back to the lesson page.</string>

    <!-- OpeningVoiceCommand !-->
    <string name="open_voice_commands_part1_intro">Welcome. In this module, you will learn how to enable voice commands. To do this, you need to perform a swipe right, then up gesture in one motion. When prompted for a voice command, say help. This will take you to the voice command help section. Explore the voice command help section, then return the tutorial by using a go back gesture or a back button if supported on your device. You may now start.</string>
    <string name="open_voice_commands_part1_outro">Well done. Next we will put some voice commands into action. Double tap to move to the next stage.</string>
    <string name="open_voice_commands_part2_intro">Now that you know some voice commands, you will learn how to increase talkback\'s reading speed by using the voice command.</string>
    <string name="open_voice_commands_part2_outro">You have completed this module. Sending you back to the lesson screen.</string>
    <string name="open_voice_commands_part2_text">Swipe right then up with one finger to open voice command again. Do this gesture, then say speak faster to make me speak faster. Move to the next element when you are done. You may now start.</string>
    <string name="open_voice_command_part2_text_end">I am now speaking faster. When you have completed listening to this text, go to the next element and select the finish button to finish the module. </string>
    <string name="open_voice_command_part2_control_text">Swipe right.</string>
    <string name="stop_count">stop_count</string>
    <string name="open_voice_command_part1_backstack">openVoiceCommandPart1</string>

    <!-- OpenNotifications !-->
    <string name="open_notifications_intro">Welcome. In this module, you will learn how to open your notification panel. Notifications are a way of letting you know that something new has happened. This is useful so you do not miss anything that might be worth your immediate attention. Notifications will appear on your device whether you are using an application or not. There are two ways to do this. First, open the notification panel by swiping down with two fingers from the top of your screen. Once you opened the notification panel, Talkback will start talking for a few seconds. Please wait until Talkback is done then follow the next instruction. You may now start.</string>
    <string name="open_notifications_feedback_1">Good job. You have opened the notification panel. Now try to close it by doing the same gesture but this time, start from the bottom of the notification tray and swipe up with two fingers."</string>
    <string name="open_notifications_feedback_2">Well done. The notification panel has been closed. Let\'s try to open it one more time. This time, open it by swiping right, then down in a single motion with one finger. Once again, please wait until Talkback is done, then follow the next instruction.</string>
    <string name="open_notifications_feedback_3">Excellent. Now close it again by swiping up from the bottom of the notification tray with two fingers</string>
    <string name="open_notifications_outro">Well done! You now know how to open and close your notification panel. The notification panel can also be used to perform many shortcuts. For example, connecting to wifi and bluetooth. You have completed the lesson. Double tap to return to the lesson page.</string>

    <!-- OpenRecentApps !-->
    <string name="open_recent_apps_part1_intro">Welcome. In this module, you will learn how to open the recents menu and open recent apps. The recents menu is a handy way to quickly switch between frequently used apps. This can be done in two different ways. Firstly, perform a swipe left then up gesture in one motion. Once completed, select and double tap the tutorial to return to the lesson. You may now start.</string>
    <string name="open_recent_apps_part1_outro">Great job. You have correctly opened the recents menu and returned to the tutorial. Now to try with a different method. Double tap to continue.</string>
    <string name="open_recent_apps_part2_intro">Try to open the recents menu using the recents button in the bottom right or bottom left corner of your phone. You can double tap this button to open the recent apps menu. If your device does not support a recents button, or you are unsure, perform a swipe left, then up gesture again to open the recents menu. Then return to the tutorial once again. You may now start.</string>
    <string name="open_recent_apps_part2_outro">Well done! You have completed the open recent apps module. Double tap to return to the lesson screen.</string>
    <string name="open_recent_apps_part1_backstack">"openrecentappspart1"</string>

    <!-- OpenTalkbackMenu !-->
    <string name="open_talkback_menu_intro">Welcome. In this module, you will learn how to open the Talkback Menu. The Talkback menu allows you use commands to read, edit text, control speech output, change Talkback settings, and more. To open the menu, perform a swipe up, then right gesture in one motion. Or a swipe down, then right gesture. You may now start. </string>
    <string name="open_talkback_menu_outro">Well done! You now know how to open and close the Talkback Menu. Once again, to do this you have to swipe up, or a swipe down gesture then swipe right immediately. You have completed the lesson. Double tap to return to the main menu.</string>
    <string name="open_talkback_menu_feedback">Great job. You have opened the Talkback menu. Feel free to navigate around to see what you can do. Once you are done, go to the bottom of the menu and exit. You may now start.</string>

    <!-- Scroll !-->
    <string name="scroll_part1_set_up">To scroll down, place two fingers on the screen at the same time, then swipe upwards with both of them. To scroll up, swipe with two fingers in the opposite direction. To finish, find the Continue button at the bottom of this vertical menu, then double tap it to continue.</string>
    <string name="scroll_part2_backstack">scrollingModulePart2</string>
    <string name="scroll_part1_intro_p1">Welcome. In this module, you will learn how to scroll through vertical and horizontal menus. Screens often contain very long lists that contain more items than the screen can show at once. Scrolling is used to go through these very long lists of items very quickly. To start, you will try scrolling through a vertical menu with</string>
    <string name="scroll_part1_intro_p2">items. To scroll down, place two fingers on the screen at the same time, then swipe upwards with both of them. To scroll up, swipe with two fingers in the opposite direction. To finish, find the Continue button at the bottom of this vertical menu, then double tap it to continue. You may now start.</string>
    <string name="scroll_part2_set_up">To scroll right, swipe left with two fingers. To scroll left, swipe with two fingers in the opposite direction. To finish, first check the checkbox at the end of the horizontal menu, then press the button at the beginning of the horizontal menu.</string>
    <string name="scroll_part2_intro">Now you will learn how to scroll through horizontal menus. When scrolling vertically, you used two fingers to swipe up and down. Now, when scrolling horizontally, you will use two fingers to swipe left and right. To scroll right, swipe left with two fingers. To scroll left, swipe with two fingers in the opposite direction. To finish the lesson, scroll to the end of the horizontal menu, and interact with the button to finish the lesson. You may now start.</string>
    <string name="scroll_part2_outro">You have completed the lesson. Sending you to the main menu.</string>

    <!-- StartStopMedia !-->
    <string name="start_stop_media_part1_outro">Great job! You have paused the video. Congratulations on completing this lesson on how to start and stop a video. Sending you back to the lesson page.</string>
    <string name="start_stop_media_part1_play">Great job! You have played the video. Now, we will try to pause the video. To pause the video, bring up the media controller and find the pause button. Double tap on the button to pause the video.</string>
    <string name="start_stop_media_part1_intro">In this tutorial, you will be learning how to start and stop a video. To start, double tap your screen to bring up the media controller and find the play button. Double tap to start playing the video.</string>

    <!-- Virtual Keyboard !-->
    <string name="virtual_keyboard_hello">hello</string>
    <string name="virtual_keyboard_part1_on_finish_typing">Great job! You have typed the word hello with the on screen keyboard. Congratulations on completing this lesson. In this lesson you have successfully learnt how to type with the on screen keyboard.</string>
    <string name="virtual_keyboard_part1_on_finish_typing_fail">Looks like you have not typed the word hello. Double tap on the screen to bring up the keyboard. Tap on the backspace button to delete the previously typed word and try typing the word hello again.</string>
    <string name="virtual_keyboard_part1_intro">In this tutorial, you will be learning how to open the on-screen virtual keyboard and type using it. To start, double tap on the screen to open the virtual keyboard. </string>
    <string name="virtual_keyboard_navigation_bar_height">navigation_bar_height</string>
    <string name="virtual_keyboard_status_bar_height">status_bar_height</string>
    <string name="virtual_keyboard_dimen">dimen</string>
    <string name="virtual_keyboard_part1_on_show_keyboard">Great job! You opened up the on screen virtual keyboard. Explore by touch to type hello using the keyboard</string>

    <!-- VoiceRecorderApp !-->
    <string name="voice_recorder_successful_recording">Well done. You have successfully made a voice recording.</string>
    <string name="voice_recorder_finish_text">You have successfully played back a recording you made. That\'s all there is right now for working with Simple Voice Recorder. The button below will finish this module.</string>
    <string name="voice_recorder_wrong_action_text">You performed the wrong action. You are supposed to do the following:</string>
    <string name="voice_recorder_play_recording_prompt">Let\'s try playing that recording. To do so, you\'ll have to switch to the recordings tab in the app and activate the recording you made. The button below will take you back to the voice recorder:</string>
    <string name="voice_recorder_wrong_bad_stage">We couldn\'t find the prompt for your last task. Please report this as a bug.</string>
    <string name="voice_recorder_intro">In this module, you\'ll be doing a few tasks in a modified version of the Simple Voice Recorder app. You can retrieve this modified app from the link below:</string>
    <string name="voice_recorder_link"><a href="https://github.com/TalkbackTutorial/voice-recorder-fork/releases/download/5.7.1-tbfork/voice-recorder-core-debug.apk">Link to the modified Simple Voice Recorder</a></string>
    <string name="voice_recorder_make_recording_intro">Your first task will be to make a recording. You\'ll open the app, start recording, and stop. There\'s no need to record any sound.</string>
    <string name="external_app_open_button">Open the app</string>
    <string name="voice_recorder_install_prompt">Once you have installed the app, activate the button below to continue.</string>
    <string name="voice_recorder_make_recording_prompt">When you open the app, you should grant it microphone permission. To start recording, press the recording button at the bottom of the main page. The button below will take you to the app.</string>

    <!-- Unsorted !-->

    <string name="wrong_action_message">You performed the wrong action. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="pushback_text">This element will push you back</string>
    <string name="final_button_mid_module_prompt">continue</string>
    <string name="final_button_end_module_prompt">finish module</string>
    <string name="challenge_card_title">End of Lesson Challenge</string>
    <string name="module_subtitle">Module %1$d</string>
    <string name="shop_title">Billy\'s Toy Shop</string>
    <string name="price_range_label">Price Range:</string>
    <string name="tennis_racquet_description">An easy-to-handle racket, ideal for intermediate or younger players transitioning from junior to adult size. Made from graphite. Increases the ball contact with the racket by 25 percent, providing more control and comfort. Specifications: Head: 102 sq. in./660 m². Corded: Yes. Cover: Yes. Length: 27 in./685 mm. String Pattern: 16 x 19. Balance: 335 mm. Stiffness: 68 RA. Rim profile: 23mm/26mm/23mm. Weight: 280 grams.</string>
    <string name="tennis_ball_description">This extra duty tennis ball is ideal for longer play on hard court surfaces. An ideal ball for all levels of tournament and recreational play.</string>
    <string name="basket_ball_description">It\'s time to take your game to the next level with this basketball - perfect for beginners as well as professionals.</string>
    <string name="teddy_bear_description">This fluffy teddy bear will be an ideal companion for your little munchkin.</string>
    <string name="princess_doll_description">Each Princess toy shines in a signature colour outfit that sparkles from the top of her bodice to the bottom of her skirt! Little dreamers will love playing out magical moments from Disney Princess movies and imagining their own fairytales with these gorgeous dolls.</string>
    <string name="plastic_castle_description">A castle that will bring hours of magical play and fun to your little one. It will encourage young children to use their creative thoughts and develop their minds. Decorated with beautiful mushrooms and features a fairy gate that opens and closes. It will help children discover new things about themselves and their world every day.</string>
    <string name="rc_car_description">Kids can engage in hours of fun playtime with this cool, 4 by 4 climbing car toy.</string>
    <string name="robot_figurine_description">Enhance your child\'s playtime experience with a touch of artificial intelligence with this cool intelligent robot toy.</string>
    <string name="unicorn_plush_description">Make a magical addition to your child\'s day with this cute unicorn plush.</string>
    <string name="plastic_kitchen_set_description">Kids will have lots of fun playing with this retro-style plastic kitchen set.</string>
    <string name="playing_cards_description">Get together with your friends and family this weekend and play exciting card games!</string>
    <string name="train_set_description">Hop on board for a fun-filled journey through the farm with this wooden train set that will teach your little one various skills.</string>
    <string name="toy_guitar_description">Delight your little musician with this guitar that is an ideal plaything to indulge in, for interactive, musical fun.</string>
    <string name="egg_description">Can I offer you a nice egg in this trying time?</string>
    <string name="basket_ball">Basket Ball</string>
    <string name="teddy_bear">Teddy Bear</string>
    <string name="princess_doll">Princess Doll</string>
    <string name="plastic_castle">Plastic Castle</string>
    <string name="rc_car">RC Car</string>
    <string name="robot_figurine">Robot Figurine</string>
    <string name="unicorn_plush">Unicorn Plush</string>
    <string name="plastic_kitchen_set">Plastic Kitchen Set</string>
    <string name="playing_cards">Playing Cards</string>
    <string name="train_set">Train Set</string>
    <string name="toy_guitar">Toy Guitar</string>
    <string name="egg">Egg</string>
    <string name="rating_label">Rating: </string>
    <string name="price_label">Price: $</string>
    <string name="purchase">Purchase</string>
    <string name="add_to_watchlist">Add to Watchlist</string>
    <string name="purchased_feedback">%1$s Purchased</string>
    <string name="added_to_watchlist_feedback">%1$s Added to Watchlist</string>
    <string name="price_range">Price Range</string>
    <string name="popup_text">Talkback is disabled. This application requires you to first enable Talkback. Tap \'open settings\' to go to the accessibility settings page, or tap \'exit\' to exit the application.</string>
    <string name="popup_display_text">Talkback is required for this application. You can enable it in the accessibility settings of your device.</string>
    <string name="exit_application">Exiting the application.</string>
    <string name="send_setting">Opening settings. Return once Talkback is enabled.</string>
    <string name="talkback_disabled">Talkback Disabled</string>
    <string name="open_settings">Open Settings</string>
    <string name="close_application">Exit</string>
    <string name="article_video_content_description">Embedded Video</string>
    <string name="article_title">The Different Memory Storage Areas of the Brain</string>
    <string name="article_date">Saturday 15th July, 2042</string>
    <string name="article_author">Author: Billy Eggman</string>
    <string name="article_paragraph1">Within the cerebral cortex, the frontal and temporal lobes are heavily involved in explicit/declarative memory processes. Episodic memories tent to be stored in the frontal lobe (particularly the pre-frontal cortex) and temporal lobe. The same can be assumed with semantic memories. Components of our memories such as visuals and sounds are stored in areas throughout the cerebral cortex. Sound is sotred in the temporal lobe, while visuals in the occipital lobe.</string>
    <string name="article_paragraph2">The hippocampus (in temporal lobe) consolidates memories, turning short term memories into long term declarative memories; semantic and episodic. It also has roles in emotional memory due to its proximity to the amygdala, and spatial memory.</string>
    <string name="article_paragraph3">The amygdala (in temporal lobe) is involved in emotional memory, and links emotions and emotional responses (such as fear and aggression) to declarative memories. This helps us remember experiences by the emotion we felt during its formation. Also involved in the formation of procedural memories.</string>
    <string name="article_paragraph4">The cerebellum is involved in motor learning and the memory of conditioned reflexes. It\'s involved in implicit memory such as procedural memories that require movement. Also has a role in spatial navigation.</string>
    <string name="article_paragraph5">Finally, language is stored in Broca\'s area in the left frontal lobe, and memory for pictures are stored in the occipital lobe.</string>
    <string name="textview">TextView</string>
    <string name="button">Button</string>

    <!-- GameMode !-->
    <string name="game_mode_title">Minigame</string>
    <string name="game_mode_subtitle">Consolidate Learnt Gestures</string>
    <string name="game_intro">Welcome. To start or end the minigame, you\'ll need to disable Talkback by holding down both volume keys on the side of your device simultaneously.</string>
    <string name="game_start">Minigame starting. Remember, to exit, hold down both volume keys on the side of your device simultaneously. To play the game, an action will be spoken for you to perform. Perform the correct gesture to score a point. The minigame will start now.</string>
    <string name="game_end">Game ended. Your final score was %1$d. Sending you to the main menu.</string>
    <string name="game_wrong_gesture">Your final score was %1$d. The correct gesture was to %2$s. Setting your score back to 0 and starting a new game.</string>
    <string name="game_read_scores">Current score is %1$d. High score is %2$d</string>
    <string name="game_new_high_score">New high score!</string>

    <!-- SandboxMode !-->
    <string name="sandbox_mode_title">Sandbox Mode</string>
    <string name="sandbox_mode_subtitle">Experiment With Gestures</string>
    <string name="sandbox_intro">Welcome. To start or end the sandbox, you\'ll need to disable Talkback by holding down both volume keys on the side of your device simultaneously.</string>
    <string name="sandbox_start">Sandbox starting. Remember, to exit, hold down both volume keys on the side of your device simultaneously. To use the sandbox, perform any gesture and the corresponding action will be spoken. The sandbox will start now.</string>
    <string name="sandbox_end">Sandbox ended. Sending you to the main menu.</string>
</resources>