<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Talkback Tutorial</string>
    <string name="lesson1_title">Lesson 1</string>
    <string name="lesson1_subtitle">Single Motion Gestures</string>
    <string name="lesson2_title">Lesson 2</string>
    <string name="lesson2_subtitle">Multi-Finger Gestures</string>
    <string name="lesson3_title">Lesson 3</string>
    <string name="lesson3_subtitle">Dual Motion Gestures</string>
    <string name="lesson4_title">Lesson 4</string>
    <string name="lesson4_subtitle">Typing</string>
    <string name="lessons">Lessons</string>
    <string name="adjust_reading_controls_part1_intro">We\'ll be learning how to adjust TalkBack\'s reading controls, which lets us make TalkBack read and navigate in different ways. TalkBack has reading modes, such as word-by-word, and navigation modes, such as jumping from header to header. When you change modes, TalkBack will speak the mode you switched to.</string>
    <string name="adjust_reading_controls_part1_prompt">To change your mode, swipe up and down in one motion. Take your time to cycle through all the choices.</string>
    <string name="adjust_reading_controls_part1_backwards_prompt">You can go backwards through the list. Swipe down then up in one motion to go through the list in the opposite direction.</string>
    <string name="adjust_reading_controls_part1_multi_finger">Modes can also be switched by swiping with three fingers horizontally to the left or to the right.</string>
    <string name="adjust_reading_controls_part1_finished_text">That\'s all there is to changing modes. The rest of this lesson covers how to use these modes. Activate the button below to finish this module.</string>
    <string name="finish_module_button">Finish module</string>
    <string name="jump_controls_intro_initial_text">The \"Controls\" reading mode allows jumping between buttons, sliders, switches, and other interactive things.</string>
    <string name="jump_controls_intro_first_prompt">Switch to the Controls reading mode and swipe down to jump to the control at the end of the page.</string>
    <string name="jump_controls_intro_next_button">Success: activate to continue</string>
    <string name="wrong_gesture_trap_message">You performed the wrong action. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="trap_text_view">This element will push you back</string>
</resources>