<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Talkback Tutorial</string>
    <string name="lesson1_title">Lesson 1</string>
    <string name="lesson1_subtitle">Single Motion Gestures</string>
    <string name="lesson2_title">Lesson 2</string>
    <string name="lesson2_subtitle">Multi-Finger Gestures</string>
    <string name="lesson3_title">Lesson 3</string>
    <string name="lesson3_subtitle">Dual Motion Gestures</string>
    <string name="lesson4_title">Lesson 4</string>
    <string name="lesson4_subtitle">Typing</string>
    <string name="lessons">Lessons</string>
    <string name="adjust_reading_controls_part1_intro">This module covers how to adjust TalkBack\'s reading controls, which lets us make TalkBack read and navigate in different ways. When you change modes, TalkBack will speak the mode you switched to.</string>
    <string name="adjust_reading_controls_part1_prompt">To change your mode, swipe up and down in one motion. Try to go through all of the options before moving on.</string>
    <string name="adjust_reading_controls_part1_backwards_prompt">You can go backwards through the list. Swipe down then up in one motion to go through the list in the opposite direction.</string>
    <string name="adjust_reading_controls_part1_multi_finger">Modes can also be switched by swiping with three fingers horizontally either to the left or to the right. Try going through the list with three finger swipes in both directions before moving on.</string>
    <string name="adjust_reading_controls_part1_finished_text">That\'s all there is to changing modes. The rest of this lesson covers how to use these modes. Activate the button below to finish this module.</string>
    <string name="finish_module_button">Finish module</string>
    <string name="jump_controls_intro_initial_text">The \"Controls\" reading mode allows jumping between buttons, sliders, switches, and other interactive things.</string>
    <string name="jump_controls_intro_first_prompt">Switch to the Controls reading mode and swipe down to jump to the next button.</string>
    <string name="wrong_gesture_trap_message">You performed the wrong action. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="trap_text_view">This element will push you back</string>
    <string name="adjust_reading_controls_part1_justification">There are reading and navigation modes. Reading modes help you read in a granular way, such as by words, paragraphs, or characters. Navigation modes help you move around more efficiently, such as by jumping from button to button.</string>
    <string name="jump_controls_intro_first_button">There\'s another button below. Jump to it.</string>
    <string name="jump_controls_intro_last_button">This is the last button. Activate it to continue.</string>
    <string name="jump_controls_intro_last_alt_button">To continue, swipe up to go to the previous button</string>
    <string name="jump_controls_intro_first_alt_button">That\'s the basics of jumping between controls. Activate to finish this module.</string>
</resources>