<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Talkback Tutorial</string>
    <string name="lessons">Lessons</string>
    <string name="adjust_reading_controls_part1_intro">This module covers how to adjust TalkBack\'s reading controls, which lets us make TalkBack read and navigate in different ways. When you change modes, TalkBack will speak the mode you switched to.</string>
    <string name="adjust_reading_controls_part1_prompt">To change your mode, swipe up and down in one motion. Try to go through all of the options before moving on.</string>
    <string name="adjust_reading_controls_part1_backwards_prompt">You can go backwards through the list. Swipe down then up in one motion to go through the list in the opposite direction.</string>
    <string name="adjust_reading_controls_part1_multi_finger">Modes can also be switched by swiping with three fingers horizontally either to the left or to the right. Try going through the list with three finger swipes in both directions before moving on.</string>
    <string name="adjust_reading_controls_part1_finished_text">That\'s all there is to changing modes. The rest of this lesson covers how to use these modes. Activate the button below to finish this module.</string>
    <string name="finish_module_button">Finish module</string>
    <string name="jump_controls_intro_initial_text">The \"Controls\" reading mode allows jumping between buttons, sliders, switches, and other interactive things.</string>
    <string name="jump_navigation_easy_prompt">Switch to the %s reading mode and swipe down to jump to the next %s.</string>
    <string name="wrong_action_message">You performed the wrong action. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="pushback_text">This element will push you back</string>
    <string name="adjust_reading_controls_part1_justification">There are reading and navigation modes. Reading modes help you read in a granular way, such as by words, paragraphs, or characters. Navigation modes help you move around more efficiently, such as by jumping from button to button.</string>
    <string name="finish_module">Finish Module</string>
    <string name="jump_text_paragraph_can">Can you can a canned can into an un-canned can like a canner can can a canned can into an un-canned can?</string>
    <string name="jump_text_paragraph_seashells">She sells seashells on the seashore. The shells she sells are seashells, I’m sure. And if she sells seashells on the seashore, Then I’m sure she sells seashore shells.</string>
    <string name="jump_text_paragraph_piper">Peter Piper picked a peck of pickled peppers; A peck of pickled peppers Peter Piper picked; If Peter Piper picked a peck of pickled peppers, Where’s the peck of pickled peppers Peter Piper picked</string>
    <string name="jump_navigation_easy_first_element">There\'s another %s below. Jump to it.</string>
    <string name="jump_navigation_easy_last_element">This is the last %s. Activate it to continue.</string>
    <string name="jump_navigation_easy_last_element_active">To continue, swipe up to the previous %s</string>
    <string name="jump_navigation_easy_first_element_active">That\'s the basics of jumping between %s. Activate to %s.</string>
    <string name="jump_headers_entity">header</string>
    <string name="jump_headers_entity_plural">headers</string>
    <string name="jump_controls_entity">control</string>
    <string name="jump_controls_entity_plural">controls</string>
    <string name="jump_links_entity">link</string>
    <string name="jump_links_entity_plural">links</string>
    <string name="final_button_mid_module_prompt">continue</string>
    <string name="final_button_end_module_prompt">finish module</string>
    <string name="jump_headers_intro_1">The \"Headers\" reading mode allows you to jump between headers, such those found before blocks of text or groups of form fields.</string>
    <string name="jump_links_intro_1">The \"Links\" navigation mode lets you jump between clickable links on a page, such as a URL.</string>
    <string name="jump_text_request_paragraph_mode">We will now learn to use each reading modes. As you have learned previously, please switch to the reading mode that says \"Paragraph\"</string>
    <string name="jump_text_paragraphs_intro">You will now learn to transition between paragraphs. A single swipe up or down will transition between different paragraphs that are on the screen. Please try it until you reach a button that says finish lesson, then double tap to finish the lesson. For your information, this will be a very long practice text so it would be easier to complete it using the Paragraph reading mode. However, you can still try out different reading modes such as Characters, Words and lines reading modes.</string>
    <string name="jump_text_paragraphs_conclusion">You have completed the lesson. To summarise, in this lesson you have learnt to use the Paragraph reading mode to navigate through the page. In the future, you can utilise these different reading modes such as Headers, Controls, Links and more, to navigate through your phone. Sending you back to the Lesson modules.</string>
    <string name="jump_text_continue_fragment_message">If you have changed reading mode to Paragraph mode, Please double tap to continue</string>
    <string name="challenge_card_title">End of Lesson Challenge</string>
    <string name="module_subtitle">Module %1$d</string>
    <string name="shop_title">Billy\'s Toy Shop</string>
    <string name="price_range_label">Price Range:</string>
    <string name="tennis_racquet_description">An easy-to-handle racket, ideal for intermediate players or young players transitioning from junior to adult size. Made from graphite. Increases the ball contact with the racket by 25 percent, providing more control and comfort. Specifications: Head: 102 sq. in./660 m². Corded: Yes. Cover: Yes. Length: 27 in./685 mm. String Pattern: 16 x 19. Balance: 335 mm. Stiffness: 68 RA. Rim profile: 23mm/26mm/23mm. Weight: 280 grams.</string>
    <string name="tennis_ball_description">This extra duty tennis ball is ideal for longer play on hard court surfaces. An ideal ball for all levels of tournament and recreational play.</string>
    <string name="basket_ball_description">It\'s time to take your game to the next level with this basketball - perfect for beginners as well as professionals.</string>
    <string name="teddy_bear_description">This fluffy teddy bear will be an ideal sleeptime or playtime companion for your little munchkin.</string>
    <string name="princess_doll_description">Each Princess toy shines in a signature colour outfit that sparkles from the top of her bodice to the bottom of her skirt! Little dreamers will love playing out magical moments from Disney Princess movies and imagining their own fairytales with these gorgeous dolls.</string>
    <string name="plastic_castle_description">A castle that will bring hours of magical play and fun to your little one. It will encourage young children to use their creative thoughts and develop their minds. Decorated with beautiful mushrooms and features a fairy gate that opens and closes. It will help children discover new things about themselves and their world every day.</string>
    <string name="rc_car_description">Kids can engage in hours of fun playtime with this cool, 4x4 climbing car toy.</string>
    <string name="robot_figurine_description">Enhance your child\'s playtime experince with a touch of artificial intelligence with this cool intelligent robot toy.</string>
    <string name="unicorn_plush_description">Make a magical addition to your child\'s day with this cute unicorn plush.</string>
    <string name="plastic_kitchen_set_description">Kids will have lots of fun playing with this retro-style plastic kitchen set.</string>
    <string name="playing_cards_description">Get together with your friends and family this weekend and play exciting card games!</string>
    <string name="train_set_description">Hop on board for a fun-filled journey through the farm with this wooden train set that will teach your little one various skills.</string>
    <string name="toy_guitar_description">Delight your little musician with this guitar that is an ideal plaything to indulge in, for interactive, musical fun.</string>
    <string name="egg_description">Can I offer you a nice egg in this trying time?</string>
    <string name="tennis_ball">Tennis Ball</string>
    <string name="tennis_racquet">Tennis Racquet</string>
    <string name="basket_ball">Basket Ball</string>
    <string name="teddy_bear">Teddy Bear</string>
    <string name="princess_doll">Princess Doll</string>
    <string name="plastic_castle">Plastic Castle</string>
    <string name="rc_car">RC Car</string>
    <string name="robot_figurine">Robot Figurine</string>
    <string name="unicorn_plush">Unicorn Plush</string>
    <string name="plastic_kitchen_set">Plastic Kitchen Set</string>
    <string name="playing_cards">Playing Cards</string>
    <string name="train_set">Train Set</string>
    <string name="toy_guitar">Toy Guitar</string>
    <string name="egg">Egg</string>
    <string name="rating_label">Rating: </string>
    <string name="price_label">Price: $</string>
    <string name="purchase">Purchase</string>
    <string name="add_to_watchlist">Add to Watchlist</string>
    <string name="purchased_feedback">%1$s Purchased</string>
    <string name="added_to_watchlist_feedback">%1$s Added to Watchlist</string>
    <string name="lesson2_challenge_intro">Welcome to Lesson 2\'s challenge. In challenges, you\'ll be presented with practical scenarios to demonstrate your new learnt skills. In this challenge, you\'ll be presented with a store. To complete the lesson, add the tennis ball and the tennis racquet to your watchlist. The tennis ball has a price of $5, and the tennis racquet has a price of $180. You may now start.</string>
    <string name="challenge_outro">You have completed the challenge. Sending you to the main menu.</string>
    <string name="price_range">Price Range</string>
    <string name="rating_content_description">Rating: %1$d stars</string>
    <string name="popup_text">Talkback is disabled. This application requires you to first enable Talkback. Tap \'open settings\' to go to the accessibility settings page, or tap \'exit\' to exit the application.</string>
    <string name="popup_display_text">Talkback is required for this application. You can enable it in the accessibility settings of your device.</string>
    <string name="exit_application">Exiting the application.</string>
    <string name="send_setting">Opening settings. Return once Talkback is enabled.</string>
    <string name="talkback_disabled">Talkback Disabled</string>
    <string name="open_settings">Open Settings</string>
    <string name="close_application">Exit</string>
    <string name="lesson4_challenge_intro">In this challenge, you\'ll be presented an article with an embedded video already playing. To complete the challenge, pause the video, and return its slider to the beginning of the video, then replay it. You may now start.</string>
    <string name="article_video_content_description">Embedded Video</string>
    <string name="article_title">The Different Memory Storage Areas of the Brain</string>
    <string name="article_date">Saturday 15th July, 2042</string>
    <string name="article_author">Author: Billy Eggman</string>
    <string name="article_paragraph1">Within the cerebral cortex, the frontal and temporal lobes are heavily involved in explicit/declarative memory processes. Episodic memories tent to be stored in the frontal lobe (particularly the pre-frontal cortex) and temporal lobe. The same can be assumed with semantic memories. Components of our memories such as visuals and sounds are stored in areas throughout the cerebral cortex. Sound is sotred in the temporal lobe, while visuals in the occipital lobe.</string>
    <string name="article_paragraph2">The hippocampus (in temporal lobe) consolidates memories, turning short term memories into long term declarative memories; semantic and episodic. It also has roles in emotional memory due to its proximity to the amygdala, and spatial memory.</string>
    <string name="article_paragraph3">The amygdala (in temporal lobe) is involved in emotional memory, and links emotions and emotional responses (such as fear and aggression) to declarative memories. This helps us remember experiences by the emotion we felt during its formation. Also involved in the formation of procedural memories.</string>
    <string name="article_paragraph4">The cerebellum is involved in motor learning and the memory of conditioned reflexes. It\'s involved in implicit memory such as procedural memories that require movement. Also has a role in spatial navigation.</string>
    <string name="article_paragraph5">Finally, language is stored in Broca’s area in the left frontal lobe, and memory for pictures are stored in the occipital lobe.</string>
</resources>